Anthony Winters

A full-stack web developer with 2+ years experience primarily in Node.js but with an interest in React.js and the front-end of applications. Coupled with 10+ years of software testing experience. Looking for a role that will allow for professional growth and to exercise current skill set, while being challenged to learn new techniques.

206-718-4515

SKILLSJavaScript

Node.js

React.js

MySQL

jQuery

GitHub

IIRA

Express.js

MongoDB

Tony.Winters0@Gmail.com LinkedIn.com/Tony-Winters GitHub.com/QuantumPhilosophy QuantumPhilosophy.org

WORK EXPERIENCE

Groupon, Seattle

Software Development Engineer in Test II — Feb 2017 - Feb 2019

- Coordinated load tests for multiple critical tier services for Super Bowl and Black Friday peak periods. Facilitating a smooth error free experience for users
- Helped make test execution self serve by building Node.js dashboard. Reducing test setup and reporting time from over 1 hour to under 15 mins

Software Test Engineer II — Jan 2016 - Jan 2017

- Wrote test suites for new features including outlines for automation tests
- Conducted test automation passes against various aspects of the site and verifying the results along with manual checks on all major browsers
- Contributed to the development of the automation framework by creating utility classes and coding automation tests
- Contributed to the improvement of the test procedures and methodologies for the development, QA and deployment processes

Software Test Engineer I — May 2015 - Dec 2015

- Contributed to the development of the automation framework used by the team by coding utility methods used by multiple test classes
- Was responsible for the organization of load testing all the team's apps and services

EDUCATION

University of Washington Certificate in Full Stack Web Development

Insight Global - Assignment at Groupon, Seattle

Quality Assurance Engineer — June 2014 - May 2015

- Conducted test automation passes against various aspects of the site and verifying the results along with manual checks on all major browsers
- Wrote test passes in TestRail for multiple projects
- Contributed to the improvement of the test methodologies, and documentation of the constantly changing feature sets

RealNetworks - Assignment at GameHouse, Seattle

Post Production OS Compatibility Tester — June 2012 - April 2013

- Maintained a computer lab consisting of legacy and current generation hardware
- Managed workflow of all incoming titles prioritizing with input from account and project managers
- Was responsible for testing each title against Build Verification Test cases on each OS specified for the title, making sure that performance was consistent for the range of the hardware versus the requirements of the title